Curtis Cook Zuni Pueblo storytelling collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series III: Photographs
  - A small crowd gathers to look at the newly published Ho'n A:wan Delapna:we ("Our Stories" self-authored stories of Zuni school children in grades 5-8, and reproduced and translated by Curtis Cook.), 1965-1978, 4" x 5" color print; AFC 2004/010: ph14 (Box 5)
  - More copies of God and Bena:we K'okshi (The Gospel of Mark in Zuni) and Suski ("Coyote"), 1965-1978, 4" x 5" color print; AFC 2004/010: ph15 (Box 5)
  - Zuni School children in Zuni reading class with Curtis Cook, 1965-1978, 3.25" x 4.5" black and white print; AFC 2004/010: ph16 (Box 5)
  - Dowa Yalanne (the sacred mountain) in winter; Curtis Cook in foreground, 1965-1978, 3.5" x 5" color print; AFC 2004/010: ph17 (Box 5)
  - Dowa Yalanne ("Corn Mountain"), 1965-1978, 3.5" x 5" color print; AFC 2004/010: ph18 (Box 5)
  - Another view of Dowa Yalanne, 1965-1978, 3.5" x 5" color print; AFC 2004/010: ph19 (Box 5)
  - Lorenzo Chavez with Curtis Cook at Ojo Caliente, 1965-1978, 5" x 7" color print; AFC 2004/010: ph20 (Box 5)